A Guide to the Edward L. Stone/Borderland Coal Company Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Edward L. Stone Personal Papers
  - Correspondence "E" - with W. J. Eynon, and Edward Epstean, 1922 -1934 (Box Box 283)
  - Correspondence "G" - with Dr. S. S. Guerrant, Dr. Henry Guppy, Mrs. James R. Guy, Zane Grey, Miss Belle da Costa Greene, Edwin O. Grover, "Greeting Cards", 1921 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 283)
  - J. M. Dulaney, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1912 -1914 (Box Box 283)
  - Walker Machine & Foundry Corp. - files contain the complete financial reports for Walker Machine & Foundry of which Stone is Director, 1926 -1931; (4 folders) (Box Box 284)
  - Correspondence "L" - with Henry Goddard Leach, A. L. Lewis, W. P. Lipscomb, The Limited Editions Club, 1930 -1938 (Box Box 285)
  - Correspondence "O, L" - with Oxford University Press, Lucy Eugenia Osborne, William Dan Orcutt, Old Colonial Roads, Wilson H. Lee, 1930 -1938 (Box Box 285)
  - Correspondence "N" - with John Nolen, E. D. North, and L. A. Nuckols, 1930 -1938 (Box Box 285)
  - Library of Congress, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 285)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co., 1930 -1938 (Box Box 285)
  - Correspondence "F" - with E. M. Funkhouser, Benjamin Franklin Society, Mrs. Charles W. Frame, Dr. Douglas Southall Freeman, Friends of the Law Library of Congress, Friends of the Princeton Library, George P. Forsdike, the Foliophiles Inc., Charles D. Fox, 1927 -1935; (3 folders) (Box Box 286)
  - American Art Assoc., 1932 -1934 (Box Box 286)
  - American Type Founders Co., 1916 -1935 (Box Box 286)
  - Correspondence "S" - with Superintendent of Documents, J. Sussman, Summers Printing Co., "Stamp," Charles J. Smith, J. A. Smith, C. Bascom Slemp, Claude A. Swanson, "Sundries," Wilbur M. Stone, South Roanoke Land Co., 1920 -1934; (3 folders) (Box Box 287)
  - Statements - financial, 1925 (Box Box 287)
  - Strikes, 1922 (Box Box 287)
  - Correspondence "N" - with A. C. Needles, A. M. Nelson, Edgar Nininger, R. C. Nichols, New York Life Insurance Co., Dr. and Mrs. John L. Newcomb, A. Edward Newton, New York Public Library, 1922 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 288)
  - Correspondence "M" - with C. Edwin Michael, Military Companies Loan, M. M. Miller, Robert Mitchell, L. Franklin Moore, 1922 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 288)
  - Japan Paper Co., 1930 -1935 (Box Box 288)
  - Miscellaneous "M-N", 1918 -1919; (4 folders) (Box Box 290)
  - Edward L. Stone miscellaneous correspondence, 1921 -1924; (5 folders) (Box Box 291)
  - Correspondence "M" - with Mrs. C. H. Murphy Jr., Mrs. Elizabeth Wells Murphy, B. P. Moulton, 1923 -1928, 1934 -1935 (Box Box 292)
  - John Henry Nash, 1926 -1934 (Box Box 292)
  - National Council for the Protection of Roadside Beauty, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 292)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1931 Miscellaneous (Box Box 293)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B-C" - with J. T. Boone, Castner Burrows & Bullitt Inc., 1914 -1915 (Box Box 294)
  - Balance sheet - E. R. Johnson Coal Mining Co., 1912 -1917 (Box Box 294)
  - E. H. Butts, 1920 -1922 (Box Box 294)
  - Correspondence "M" - with J. L. Morris, and material concerning Paul Morand, 1931 (Box Box 294)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, 1927 -1931 (Box Box 294)
  - E. Morrell, 1933 -1935 (Box Box 294)
  - Stenographer's Transcript - commission on the advisability of establishing a liberal arts college for women, 1929 (Box Box 294)
  - Correspondence "I" - with L. A. Ireland, and the International Press Exhibition, 1927 -1934 (Box Box 294)
  - J. C. Cassell - correspondence between Stone and Cassell, 1922 -1930; (3 folders) (Box Box 296)
  - Correspondence "H" - with Fairfax Harrison, and J. M. Harris Jr., 1924 -1936 (Box Box 296)
  - Harvard University - including copies of the Harvard Economic Review forecasting business conditions for 1922 - 1924, 1922 -1936 (Box Box 296)
  - Correspondence "Ba" - topics: Babson's Report, Bachrach Inc., baggage, Bailey Banks & Biddle, W. G. Baldwin & Co., bank statements, Bankers' Loan & Investment Co., 1920 -1924 (Box Box 297)
  - Correspondence "Ba" - topics: J. Well Barker, W. T. Barron & Co., Bartlett Orr Press, Dr. Barker, W. S. Battle, 1920 -1929 (Box Box 297)
  - Correspondence "Be" - topics: The Beckoning Land, W. B. Bevill, Bellevue-Stratford, Bent Mountain Apple & Cold Storage Co., James S. Bell, J. F. Berkes, Mrs. Anna P. Bell, 1916 -1929 (Box Box 297)
  - James M. Bell Stone & Co. - clothing store advertisements, 1922 -1932 (Box Box 297)
  - E. L. Stone - monthly statements - Stone's financial statements, 1923 -1925 (Box Box 298)
  - Notes - E. L. Stone's notes to himself and personal miscellaneous correspondence, 1927 -1928 (Box Box 298)
  - Correspondence "D" - topics: Lester Douglas, and Stone Printing Directory, 1919, 1932 (Box Box 299)
  - Correspondence "E" - with Burton Emmett, T. Edison Inc., H. Spencer Edmunds, Education, H. C. Elliott, 1920 -1935 (Box Box 299)
  - Correspondence "U" - topics: United States Daily, U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1932 -1934 (Box Box 299)
  - Virginia Delegation - delegates from Virginia State Chamber of Commerce report on Great Britain visit, 1930 (Box Box 299)
  - Receipts, 1936 -1938 (Box Box 299)
  - Nations' business, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 299)
  - Correspondence "D" - topics: L. L. Downing; Dodd, Mead & Co.; Dog brushes; Winfield T. Durbin; Frank L. Drew, 1920 (Box Box 300)
  - Dog's Mouth - fountain in downtown Roanoke which Stone did an article on, 1920 (Box Box 300)
  - Thomas E. Donnelley, 1920 -1934 (Box Box 300)
  - August Dietz - Dietz Printing Co., 1924 -1934 (Box Box 300)
  - "O.K."- Stone Printing on the derivation of the slang "O.K." for all correct, 1934 -1935 (Box Box 300)
  - Personal correspondence "C, J" - with Dr. W. C. Jones, Junior Women's Club, E. P. Chamberlayne, 1924 -1936 (Box Box 301)
  - Personal Correspondence "H" - with W. P. Hazlegrove, J. Alton Hathcer, and Felix Hargrett, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 301)
  - Paul Johnston - book correspondence; Johnston is editor of the Book Collectors' Packet, 1932 -1933 (Box Box 301)
  - Johnson Service Co. - correspondence with company which specializes in temperature and humidity regulation and control systems, 1920 -1934 (Box Box 301)
  - Joyce, Agnes, Maxine, and Tony - correspondence with friends, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 301)
  - Personal correspondence "H" - with George K. Hebb (a printer who is complaining about the N.R.A. codes), Edgar D. Hellweg, Ruth Henderson, Marguerite C. Hersey, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 302)
  - Ward Edwards - personal correspondence, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 302)
  - Mrs. Gertrude Hills - correspondence with a friend of the Stone family who specializes in cataloguing personal libraries, 1930 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 302)
  - Letters and notes taken on reading material, 1927 -1930; (2 folders) (Box Box 302)
  - Walker Machine & Foundry Corp. - financial statements and business correspondence; Stone is on the Board of Directors, 1931 -1937 (Box Box 303)
  - Washington & Lee University - correspondence between Stone and Lee School of Journalism, 1923 -1936 (Box Box 303)
  - Washing machines - advertisements, 1919 -1921 (Box Box 303)
  - John Wanamaker - jewelry advertisements, 1922 -1934 (Box Box 303)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1920 -1932 (Box Box 303)
  - "Uncle Wat" - a publication of Stone Printing, 1928, 1932 (Box Box 303)
  - John S. Watson, 1921 (Box Box 303)
  - Personal correspondence "C" - with Rev. Isaac Cannaday, Monsieur Edouard Champion, Con P. Curran, M. M. Caldwell, John J. Carney, J. E. Catlin, catalogues, 1913 -1933 (Box Box 304)
  - Earnest Elmo Calkins - personal correspondence, 1927 -1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 304)
  - Civic Development Department, 1929 -1931 (Box Box 304)
  - Personal correspondence "H" - with Mr. Leigh Hanes, Mr. and Mrs. Lynn Hammond, Don P. Halsey, 1927 -1935 (Box Box 304)
  - Charity miscellaneous - charity literature, 1923 -1930; (3 folders) (Box Box 305)
  - Correspondence "G" - with Garden Clubs, Fred W. and Harry Gage, 1932 -1936 (Box Box 306)
  - Don and Mary Gates - personal correspondence, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 306)
  - Clippings and comments, 1929 -1931; (3 folders) (Box Box 306)
  - Stocks and bonds, 1916 (Box Box 307)
  - Claude A. Swanson - Senator from Virginia, 1916 (Box Box 307)
  - Stone's Efficiency Club - organized by employees of Stone Printing Co. to promote greater efficiency, 1916 (Box Box 307)
  - Al A. Stone Jr. - Stone's nephew who works at Stone Printing, 1920 -1932; (2 folders) (Box Box 308)
  - Miss Gertrude Whiting - personal correspondence, 1932 -1934 (Box Box 308)
  - J. P. Whitehead, 1933 (Box Box 308)
  - Correspondence "W" - miscellaneous, 1933 -1934 (Box Box 308)
  - Advertising Federation of America, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 309)
  - Miscellaneous statements - Edward Stone - financial records, including complete monthly records, 1933 -1936 (Box Box 309)
  - Addresses and key to Stone's file - contains a list of file topics, no date (Box Box 309)
  - Correspondence "C" - topics: Crittenton League, Confederate Reunion, Commerce Street Property, W. W. Coe, Commissioner of Revenue, Connoisseur Tobacco Co., Cookey Johnston Inc., J. T. Cottrell, H. H. Cook, Commonwealth of Virginia, Lieut. Henry Coquelet, A. B. Colvin, 1911 -1926 (Box Box 310)
  - Correspondence "F" - topics: Walter Fishburn, Blair J. Fishburn, Mrs. C. L. Fishburn (Aunt Callie), Mrs. Henriette Fallwell, James E. Farrell, Albert W. Finlay, and Fiftieth Anniversary of the city of Roanoke, Fairview Cemetery Co., F. C. Fairholme, Dr. J. B. Fackenthal, Charles C. Fleming, Jean R. Ferguson, First National Bank of Miami, 1922 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 310)
  - Correspondence "J" - topics: Mr. F. M. Jolly and Johnson-Carper Furniture Co. (Stone sells all stock in company and resigns from Board of Directors), 1922 -1929 (Box Box 310)
  - Mrs. Edward L. Stone - personal correspondence, 1921 -1929 (Box Box 310)
  - Shenandoah Life Insurance Co., 1921 -1931 (Box Box 310)
  - Correspondence "D" - topics: J. M. Darden, L. L. Davis, Davis Photographer, Frank E. Davis, Day & Night Bank, Davey Tree Expert Co., Dept. of Highways, Democratic National Convention, deeds, 1921 -1933 (Box Box 311)
  - Correspondence "C" - topics: circular letters, Chancellor Day, Citizens Alliance, cigars, 1920 -1923 (Box Box 311)
  - Joseph P. Day - real estate, 1929 (Box Box 311)
  - Davis & Stephenson - insurance, 1922 -1934 (Box Box 311)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A", 1932 -1935 (Box Box 312)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-E", 1932 -1935 (Box Box 312)
  - Monthly statements - financial, 1923 (Box Box 313)
  - Detailed monthly statements - financial, 1926 (Box Box 313)
  - Personal statements, 1917, 1918, 1919 (Box Box 313)
  - Civic Improvement Committee - Chamber of Commerce, 1929 -1930 (Box Box 314)
  - Correspondence "A"- topics: Aunspaugh family, Gustave Anjou, Mrs. Ester Andrews, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 314)
  - United States---Chamber of Commerce - correspondence, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 314)
  - Archaeological Institute, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 314)
  - Roanoke - topics: Roanoke Little Theater league, Roanoke Public Library, Rotary Club of Roanoke, 1930 -1936 (Box Box 315)
  - Mr. and Mrs. R. Hugh Roberts, 1930 -1938 (Box Box 315)
  - Sally Chilton Ryan - personal correspondence, 1928 -1934 (Box Box 315)
  - William Edwin Rudge and Mrs. Rudge, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 315)
  - Times World Co. - Roanoke, 1922 -1934 (Box Box 315)
  - Correspondence "R"- topics: William E. Rudge's Sons, Bessie Carter Randolph, Randolph Macon College, The Rosenbach Co., C. P. Rollins, Miss Mary Rogers, 1930 -1930 (Box Box 315)
  - Correspondence "W" - topics: W. L. Woodward, Lawrence C. Wrath, Rolla Wells, Women's Civic Betterment Club, 1917-1932 (Box Box 316)
  - Y. M. C. A., 1921 -1930 (Box Box 316)
  - Y. W. C. A., 1922 -1932 (Box Box 316)
  - Miscellaneous - topics: Tuskegee Normal Institute, Yellowstone Park Trip, 1912 -1916 (Box Box 316)
  - Correspondence "B" - topics: book plates, Brighton Hotel, Daniel M. Brady, W. W. Boxley, Branch & Co., Blosser Co., I. H. Blanchard, Blackstone Hotel, Academy of Political Science Booster Club, Boys Club, Marietta Boone, J. B. Botts, Blair Bolling, J. W. Bothwell, J. O. Boatwright, J. D. Bowyer, 1914 -1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 317)
  - Miscellaneous, 1915 -1919 (Box Box 317)
  - Building proofs, Stone Printing & Mfg. Co. - photographs of Stone Printing, no date (Box Box 317)
  - Boy Scouts, 1920 -1930 (Box Box 317)
  - Edward L. Stone - miscellaneous correspondence, 1917 -1913 (Box Box 317)
  - Blind - Committee to Assist, 1924 -1928 (Box Box 317)
  - Correspondence "S" - topics: T. B. Shannon, Shenandoah Life Insurance Co., Miss Jessie Skeen, Bruce P. Shepherd, Shenandoah National Park, Shenandoah Club, Salvation Army, St. Christopher, M. U. M. Salie, Sabean Society, Robert F. Salade, C. William Schneidereith, 1913 -1932; (2 folders) (Box Box 318)
  - Shorthand notes, no date (Box Box 318)
  - Correspondence "U" - topics: U.S. Geological Survey, U.S. Senate, Union, 1921 -1933 (Box Box 318)
  - University Club, 1921 -1926 (Box Box 318)
  - Typothetae - United of America, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 318)
  - Income tax return matters, 1921 -1930; (2 folders) (Box Box 319)
  - Edward L. Stone - miscellaneous correspondence, 1917 -1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 319)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1933 -1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 319)
  - Harvard Address, 1912 (Box Box 320)
  - Cotton Cloth & Paper, 1931 -1932 (Box Box 320)
  - Correspondence "S", 1933 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 320)
  - Correspondence "S" - topics: State Legislation, St. Paul Normal & Industrial School, Strass-Persinger Co., 1916 -1926 (Box Box 321)
  - William R. Stackhouse, 1921 -1924 (Box Box 321)
  - W. C. Stephenson - correspondence, 1921 -1932 (Box Box 321)
  - Charles Stultz, Mr. E. L. Stone's driver - letter of recommendation for Mr. Stultz by Stone, 1923 -1930 (Box Box 321)
  - Correspondence "S-T" - topics: Southwest Virginia Historical Society, M. Soloman, Southern Good Roads, Sons of Confederate Veterans, Mrs. E. L. Stone, Harmon Stone, Mr. Al A. Stone, Title Guarantee Trust & Savings Bank, 1914 -1933 (Box Box 322)
  - Correspondence "S" - topics: John Harmon Stone, Miss Katherine Stone, Miss M. F. Stone, 1920 -1932 (Box Box 322)
  - Correspondence "W", 1931 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 322)
  - Walker Machine & Foundry Corp. - correspondence and financial statements, 1932 -1934 (Box Box 322)
  - Correspondence "W" - topics: W. M. H. Williamson, Mrs. Stephen Williams, David L. Williams, Willing & Co., Wichita Eagle Press, C. W. Wade, Charles F. Warde, Westmoreland Club, Wiegman & Co., Walter Reed Hospital, Whaley Eaton Service, Whitehead & Hoag Co., J. V. Wenberg, Ira Welch, Julius S. Weyl, Whitaker & Co., Jack Wilson, G. O. Wilkins, R. H. Wills, Wilke Pipe Shop, Sexton Wilkerson, 1913 -1933; (2 folders) (Box Box 323)
  - War Saving Stamps, 1918 -1921 (Box Box 323)
  - Correspondence "V" - topics: Virginia State Library, Virginia Workmen's Compensation Law, Virginia Good Roads Assoc., V.M.I., Victoria Hotel, 1916 -1931 (Box Box 323)
  - V.P.I. - Stone's correspondence with personnel of Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1921 -1932 (Box Box 323)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Assoc. - correspondence and newsletters, 1930 -1934 (Box Box 323)
  - Photographs, no date; (2 folders) (Box Box 324)
  - Thomas Clemmitt, Baltimore, Md., 1917 -1933 (Box Box 324)
  - Book plates, no date (Box Box 324)
  - Columbia Planograph Co. - correspondence concerning Roanoke County map, 1930 (Box Box 324)
  - Correspondence "C" - topics: Cost System letters, Conference on Higher Education, John Clancy, 1915, 1921, 1927 (Box Box 324)
  - Correspondence "R" - topics: Ashton Reniers, Ruth C. Reeves, Whitelaw Reid, William Reydel, T. W. Richardson, Dr. John Kirk Richardson, O. W. Riegel, Roanoke City Public Schools, Roanoke Community Fund, Roanoke College, Roanoke Gun Club, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 325)
  - J. Stearns Cushing, 1913 (Box Box 325)
  - Menu Cards, 1906, 1916 -1917 (Box Box 325)
  - Realty Improvement, 1921 -1933 (Box Box 325)
  - Miscellaneous "A", 1913 -1914 (Box Box 326)
  - Alexander Hamilton Institute, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 326)
  - R. C. and Frederick Aunspaugh, 1909 -1912 (Box Box 326)
  - American Civic Assoc., 1909 -1914 (Box Box 326)
  - Correspondence "B" -- topics: J. D. Bowman, William J. H. Boetcker, S. F. Bowser, Burroughs Adding Machine, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 327)
  - E. T. Barrows Co., 1909 -1910 (Box Box 327)
  - Miscellaneous "B", 1909 -1913; (2 folders) (Box Box 327)
  - Mr. and Mrs. James A. Blane, 1909 -1913; (2 folders) (Box Box 327)
  - Joseph A. Turner, 1932 (Box Box 329)
  - Robert B. Tunstall - personal correspondence, 1929 -1933; (2 folders) (Box Box 329)
  - Correspondence "T'' - topics: Mrs. Pearl Tunstall, C. D. Traphagen, Traffic Ordinance, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 329)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "G, J", 1904 -1910 (Box Box 330)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1904 -1914 (Box Box 330)
  - Correspondence "P" - topics: postal matters, John Garland Pollard, 1922 -1933 (Box Box 331)
  - E. Alexander Dowell - personal correspondence, 1928 -1933 (Box Box 331)
  - Correspondence "T" - topics: Alfred W. Pollard, Tiffany & Co., Thurman & Boone, Themelis, 1921 -1934 (Box Box 331)
  - Poems, 1922 -1926; (2 folders) (Box Box 331)
  - Correspondence "P" - topics: Princeton University Library, Press of the Pioneers, Mrs. William J. Prout, Maria F. Parkinson, Mr. Holcombe Parkes, George C. Peery, William Pfaff, President - U.S., Mrs. Henry Price, Irma Frances Price, Miss Page Price, 1917 -1936; (2 folders) (Box Box 333)
  - Philobiblon - Herbert Reichner - book correspondence concerning German magazine Philobiblon, 1930 -1933 (Box Box 333)
  - Walker Machine & Foundry Corp., 1920 -1921 (Box Box 335)
  - James P. Woods, 1916 -1921 (Box Box 335)
  - Charles Warde, 1925 (Box Box 335)
  - Westmoreland Club, 1910, 1920 (Box Box 335)
  - Waldorf Astoria, 1920 (Box Box 335)
  - Boy Scouts, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 338)
  - Dr. Barker and other Baltimore letters, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 338)
  - Harry A. Barnitz, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 338)
  - Biltmore Industries - clothing samples, 1920 (Box Box 338)
  - Miscellaneous "A-B", 1913 -1915 (Box Box 339)
  - Addresses and articles, 1912 -1915; (2 folders) (Box Box 339)
  - Miscellaneous - topics: New York Talking Machine Co., W. H. Thomas, Tennessee Society in New York, L. S. Randolph, Gooch Vaughan, Subject 180, C182, 1910 -1920; (2 folders) (Box Box 340)
  - Virginia & Tennessee Telephone Co., Roanoke, Va.; Virginia Ore & Lumber Co., Times Investment Corp., 1905 -1915 (Box Box 340)
  - Miscellaneous "K, L, M, N, P, R, S, T, V, W", 1904 -1915 (Box Box 341)
  - L. B. Davis, 1918 (Box Box 342)
  - War Savings Stamp Executive Committee, 1918 (Box Box 342)
  - Loyalty cards - War Savings Stamp Clubs, 1918 (Box Box 342)
  - Miscellaneous "F, H, G, B, C, K, J", 1918 (Box Box 342)
  - Correspondence "G" - topics: W. D. Gresham, G. G. Gooch, M. L. Gordon, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 342)
  - Claude R. Davenport - Executive Secretary of the U.S. National War Savings Committee, 1918 (Box Box 342)
  - Roanoke Cycle Co. - advertisements, 1907 -1911 (Box Box 342)
  - Clippings, poetry, etc., 1918 (Box Box 342)
  - Miscellaneous letters, 1916 -1917; (3 folders) (Box Box 344)
  - Miscellaneous, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 345)
  - Automobile letters, 1915 (Box Box 345)
  - American Bank Notes Co., 1911 -1914 (Box Box 345)
  - American Printer, 1909 -1915 (Box Box 345)
  - American Anti-Boycott Assoc., 1912 -1915 (Box Box 345)
  - Miscellaneous letters - bills and receipts, 1904 -1914; (2 folders) (Box Box 349)
  - Bureau of the Census - Census of Manufacturers, 1914 (Box Box 350)
  - Babson's reports, 1913 -1916 (Box Box 350)
  - Miscellaneous, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 350)
  - Theodore C. Brooks, 1915 -1917 (Box Box 350)
  - Alleghany Club, 1911 -1917 (Box Box 352)
  - American Automobile Assoc., 1916 -1917 (Box Box 352)
  - American Civic Assoc., 1916 (Box Box 352)
  - Associated Advertising Clubs of the World - correspondence, 1916 -1917 (Box Box 352)
  - American Anti-Boycott Assoc., 1915 -1917 (Box Box 352)
  - Correspondence "N-O" - topics: Fred B. Neely, National Regulation Co., National Association of Credit Men, National Counsel for Industrial Defense, Oregon-Washington Land Co., 1909 -1912 (Box Box 353)
  - Newspaper comments and clippings, 1909 -1912 (Box Box 353)
  - Miscellaneous "N", 1910 -1912 (Box Box 353)
  - Persons to whom "Historic Shrines of Virginia" have been sent, no date (Box Box 354)
  - Paul Johnston's book collector's packet, 1932 (Box Box 354)
  - New York Southern Society, 1931 -1934 (Box Box 354)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S", 1930 -1936 (Box Box 354)
  - The Dance of Death translations, 1930 -1936 (Box Box 354)
  - August Dietz - personal correspondence, 1930 -1932 (Box Box 354)
  - H. W. E. Storey - personal correspondence, 1904 -1908 (Box Box 354)
  - Civic Betterment, 1907 -1908 (Box Box 354)
  - Correspondence "G" - topics: garage, golf, General Acoustic Co., 1913 -1914 (Box Box 356)
  - Miscellaneous "L-M, T-Z", 1914 -1915 (Box Box 356)
  - First National Bank, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 356)
  - W. F. C. Fellers - personal correspondence, 1909 -1915 (Box Box 356)
  - Robert and Lawrence Fell, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 356)
  - Gratis Fund - charity and donations, 1912 -1915 (Box Box 356)
  - Miscellaneous, 1916 (Box Box 357)
  - Associated Charities, 1916 (Box Box 357)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1916 (Box Box 357)
  - Associated Advertising Clubs of the World, 1916 (Box Box 357)
  - Automobile letters, 1916 (Box Box 357)
  - Automobile road, 1912 (Box Box 358)
  - Miscellaneous "A", 1912 (Box Box 358)
  - Miss Julia Aunspaugh, 1909 -1910 (Box Box 358)
  - Thomas Aunspaugh, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 358)
  - Automobile letters, 1912 (Box Box 358)
  - Ninth Avenue property, 1911 -1913 (Box Box 360)
  - Osceola Lodge, 1910 -1914 (Box Box 360)
  - Automobile letters, booklets, etc., 1914 (Box Box 361)
  - Correspondence "M" - topics: J. E. M. Hanckel, Hinsch Coal & Coke Co., Frank A. Hill, Henderson Coal Co., John T. Hesser Coal Co., W. J. Hamilton Coal Co., A. R. Hatfield, 1905 -1908 (Box Box 362)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1909 -1912 (Box Box 362)
  - Correspondence "G" - topics: Hon. Carter Glass, The Ginn Co., Glenmore Coal Co., G. G. Gooch, Goodman Ice & Fuel Co., William R. Graham, Goodrich, 1904 -1908 (Box Box 362)
  - Correspondence "J" - topics: George P. Johnson; Jewett, Bigelow & Brooks, Jeffry Mfg. Co., 1905 -1908 (Box Box 362)
  - Miscellaneous - topics: Virginia Ore & Lumber Co., Tariff Printers Society of America, taxes - county, city, and state, W. Garrison Wood, 1927 -1931 (Box Box 363)
  - Kenneth Y. Umberger and Miller Ritchie - contains a biography of Edward L. Stone written by two students at Roanoke College, 1932 (Box Box 363)
  - James P. Woods, Roanoke, Va., 1921 -1931 (Box Box 363)
  - Clifton A. Woodrum, 1928 -1938 (Box Box 363)
  - Tennessee Society, 1924 -1926 (Box Box 363)
  - Daniel Berkeley Updike, 1925 -1935 (Box Box 363)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1912 -1913 (Box Box 365)
  - Miscellaneous "W,Y", 1922 -1926 (Box Box 365)
  - Miscellaneous "U-V", 1920 -1924 (Box Box 365)
  - Miscellaneous "A, B, E, F, N, P", 1914 -1918 (Box Box 367)
  - Correspondence "F" - topics: financial papers, Farmers & Merchant Bank, Charles R. Fishburn, E. B. Fishburn, the Efficiency Society, 1914 (Box Box 367)
  - F. E. Foster, Hotel Roanoke, 1914 (Box Box 367)
  - Horace M. Engle, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 367)
  - J. B. Fishburn, 1909 -1915 (Box Box 367)
  - Printed matter, etc., 1918 (Box Box 368)
  - Miscellaneous letters regarding U.S. War Savings Committee, 1918; (2 folders) (Box Box 368)
  - Plan of organization suggested, no date (Box Box 368)
  - Miscellaneous "A", 1922 -1925 (Box Box 369)
  - Miscellaneous "B", 1924 -1926; (2 folders) (Box Box 369)